in the midst a tame one of the
refraction of nature at all begun so
reflection let me see the ball tonight
you've attained the macadam refraction
already let be easy kind of ie D and
then I Lowe's and they can mother the
Colleen the Chiron enough of an MIT
really should be can be throwing ever
que para you not a strapped in what she
endured every sectional now you would
have a look actually done the Prada
honor but the cause generally discuss
again other kicks ominous news are about
to worry 90 percentage of catch over the
calendar and a really a question to our
code really care about your question
sorry pariah
nearly chair along at a party super
boost a single prepared on oily and oh
nothing or the no quitter okay
whether Chapel to come on any question
answering an idea delivery alone upon
the England also the guidance are one
Augustine Oliver no future
so first accosted honor what do you mean
by refractive index second question
wherever the distinguish between
absolute refractive index and relate to
you will fly to index okay first Justin
you know what do you mean by the
frighteners second question distinguish
between absolute refractive index and
relate to refractive index okay
either she'll to allow you to talk you
can lock Oh Staniel on your equations
are kinda problem are correlated so we
get explanation would a note you cap now
second question the more refreshed in
the vertex are they about the top
accordion bellows of refraction so give
a brief note on loss of refraction of
Rho D cap because to nebula is another
party chip once a methanol is a big gap
in the dense a problem I discuss a book
protego another Nokia another question
if a namaha goes Chandni right we got
the video content in your dresser net
lingula and Saruman and geese India and
England and select
timeless endian an english-irish Emily
okay permanent goes to the mechanical on
our hua Nabokov your second or third cap
so topping Lake you've up a fraction of
late I'm not carrying a topic it have
cook on by the reflection I'm in the day
and then reflection the word of the
reflection on a lady a little she told
me a little ponytail it will be cheated
out of that be other reflective bounce a
the way yeah like I nobody can appear in
the
fracture world on a bouncing back off
late when heat on a suitable surface it
is called as reflection about indefinite
minerals provided to our killer
diversely a novel anomalous specific
word to the curved mirrors a little
concave and convex mirror a topic in any
in the number of another para la vie
fractionally about refraction first of
all we should know what is explanation
of refraction let refraction a little
explanation and a no alibi witness of
the camera
refraction simply means when late
travels from one medium to another it
actual deviates from this part of
propagation this phenomena is called as
refraction another negative would
immediately no matter we did flicky
propagator submit the move into some
ether and the path deviate around under
are then every can I pay around on the
refraction of you know anybody can I bet
on it refraction but I'm going to
condone really kind of a refraction
which is let's say we here experiment
under one I say the experiment Donna but
it's your yeah glass silica I never the
penicillin said to you know or - no you
can never take it GRE changer ammonia
now fill that glass with water or any or
any other liquids one condition is that
it should be transfer a lady carnal
Alana
so transparent idler headings are
liquids renew her vows affiliate our
feeling that glass with this transfer
and mediums such as water you can see
that now
we feel like the pencil is actually
broken pins in doubt path know coming or
other it sure that your broker pencil
moving in the broken schedulable under
vacuum mailbag American illegally
collected taxes on you pin down the
director at eleven slim karna but not
the lecture your deviation record
anomaly they take a hard-nosed China
number could talk you Tamara pencil
Nonna are others activate another lace
race non-arabic under Kevin bill the
second stage really late in it army
Dorota probably this been a lake you on
the in the tournament on delicate body
to travels from one medium to another oh
no a one winter owner Anya I would have
a tunnel out of poverty
al we're nobody other it's a deviation
of you know anybody
refraction texts to go jogging I expect
you till it actually exam or indirect
and apparel area court sorry get which
we will discuss a bit in their first
year coin a bucket full of water to
cuddle a calico any Alesia in England
India with your I to say it about water
trying to pick up the coin in one go
did you succeeded in picking up the coin
in England they are kept in the tire of
coin I am in a condition with your eye
to a side above Arthur trying to pick up
the coin one going on air Buccaneer man
look at this or still say it is no no no
keep it
and the coin Pokeno car what did he go
sorry they were like a corner one okay
ah ray silicon 32 refractive innovation
can take in a little level the water
load of on the pin arrow on the Pina
Colada pookie a direction molecule
number experts can yourself table coin
their position and right cap okay
other Walton art Anoka actor 10.8 place
enlarge the shadow bottle table and put
a coin in it okay molded cup a swirl of
it opening application value public
board I will call you again okay in
everything I they could be making
another cup some takoyaki Condon leaking
I'm going karna via one every little
coin car not even out running will stop
here in the high road engine your friend
in order later I don't you do a little
swirl or camera so I'm going to push in
Mar mother above like you I'd luckily
Emory happening okay we're not gonna
feel anymore
you know pushing marble Eponine Colonel
coin or addition well luckily water
Filippo cooing but then a puree risotto
ever Damien thorn I'm gonna come up
another eerie fractional phenomenon
next to activity draw a thick straight
line in ink over a sheet of white paper
placed on table place a glass slab over
the lane in such a way that one office
it just makes an angle with the length
look at the portion of the line under
the slab from sense what do you observe
that's the lane under the glass room
appear to be been that they've just
let's place the glass web says that it
is normal to the link what do you so no
that's the part of the lane under the
glass
let up you're bent look at the lane from
top of the glass slab that's the part of
the lane beneath the slab appear to be
raised
why does this happen he acted him who
will discuss the end actually they
protected in 10.10 ceramic out of the
discuss area turn out a new de práctica
later one really moon and on this cherry
mean you're tardy - neck already
activity or night in the low another
examine over a million acaba remember
you better eat 10.10 no other x i'm your
pardon on and jewels you wanted to yeah
okay stop it let go up the fraction
through it like angular glass slab what
are them so big gap you would actually
the practical session on IV cody nominal
island Nellie Wyllie
number factor last lab available and La
Mora you look at a circular section on i
do toodank a cutie after that but yet
it's a yeah but Julia okay anyway there
were a glass level in Java I really
would he feel done that should
paperweight turn loose in the form of a
surplus glass no matter how many you
could say yeah har Nakuru video I took
two I'll link a partner and I pass away
don't do a single issue yeah keep on our
car on the car on the robot never shall
begin what I'm gonna say into this
rectangle right a glass slam would come
is it a white sheet of paper and I made
a place here okay now that Cal anomaly
your glass slab under to the power Jana
you know within yourself number two can
be run when silica rectangle shape will
accompany other yeah and I would have
gotten to meet you
okay in it and the last level digital
digital director loss between our help
in silouette say the board out clean and
see the terminal in the opinion it can
be low and opinionated a way in
the variety Lane Li Yundi mean pin 0 EF
nila pointer Nellie and if outer and
ourselves dunya or underpin which
opinion straight plane and we don't know
whether EF in Allah self the easels are
trippin nature F nose atropine nature
into the glass slab prodigy in an
acknowledgment across Thunder I'm
thinking whatever ebar the beginning a
loo area in the tea glass slab and hulu
degree in ilocano cup if what I want a
glass slab into ordinary line not Anoka
EEP in Negron oka in the tuk-tuk come on
okay buddy on up in up plz and the AEF
nulla poena you wouldn't know combo but
I would
everything will be new I didn't say that
it might be new UK and that's the end of
it you would have to be never good to
you
last lap with you eople or DeLuca it's
like I've been able to put in okay and
then you know combo uh yes Filipino
encoder Locarno gonna and that EU from
the stray typed everybody on a card
another not an errand okay I reckon I
mean you're feeling on apini rack on our
an English pin devotee I got older I
tried to be mean with the straight
language I got it
in England personally class levels
market you know EU a phone in a glass a
glass slab in the ABN Allah but another
is it CD the lapatin upon amber on the
ABL apart the Kiev in early it's me some
facilities and I could lift up as a boil
then number tend to be in its energy you
to up in the whatever nobody wanted
appointing you really going to play I've
been and I'm learning a lot to join
critic another shitty Kiev know the fog
and the part are you daughter plain
sight order currents in mother ship and
entirely
efe eats free playing horn in the peewee
table is it we had a surface really time
I would another so they can see it
actually I would they got read earlier
you wouldn't know in Arianna previous
episode until they even in the corner of
the in area where another about to DVD
where a positional Odeon another parents
leveled up or instant revenue as he till
you would have me listen right didn't
emerge in reallocator eme RG and the
emergent right up emergent area meringue
Aradhana
he better Buddha Donna already
refraction not ammu
I mean you dinner with fractional Jim
Curran to good assumption I am herbs in
the way I will get out if the refracted
ray you don't frak - Briana specific
Nemo what is it
emergent event whatever it is already
fraction of no never can tell about the
pvat we into the for nothing any you
know about the DVD the Watsu moody and
over a year laying there right is it
again I'm gonna Okinawa Danny Lane
trying to say like your city whatever
today
so again desire is across on the
refraction approximately okay some can I
avoid Akana oh no they lo al exam
commander hiding a rectangular glass
level
the net the more could a laser lay
bebe's namishyami to boil turn a
carnival I'm gonna try say yeah it never
gets old cilia I don't even think I'm
gonna car Nostrum come III my cell are
dripping as I read on it yeah Philippine
never liked being Jay Riecke if no
question a little in the dig last
language city burden oka upon me India
feelin air and I'm goofy on a selfie leg
once never Miami what I fear the under
share later been down on the road in an
inferior you've been honey glass never
become an encoder period on that machine
he wasn't Ocampo a glass remember too
much of easily feel is even if the
actual Carnegie lanes in a curriculum
glass never Kimball and though the
change any key experience a number of
the water fence indicates Tilikum
couldn't Amish up is there a mare is no
chemical no observer on other I'm gonna
need a man that should know Kannada
Norman today a tsunami already we
absolutely other thought you can't go
either this particular question or a
bike somewhere under sample I'm not
normally without killing yeah change in
the other you refraction articular
reflection on curricula are a street
take the time to keep oh it's like a PE
bring in a vortex a majority Kira really
could be slab in an air a man with a
high-tech no key Hanoi strange ending
roll it out Amanda every day on object
out then I cannot really change June
down okay the value on my life other got
a questionable dog like to see me awake
Anya I'm gonna see me Mulder a floor
correct subbu team alien on tone what
Islam compact in the car left no cathode
about that today Casey also be personal
day he they want the most cynical not so
if we know it's in the universe if what
any peanuts really care for a glass slab
with you but I'm not you mean character
that you what a ten-inning Rita
yeah other you changing everybody
Pendleton I don't know my lord and I'm
gonna oh you're a stupid idea or the
deviation on Dahlia other reflection on
angular Shari the fractional English a
reflection on even though everyone only
do the two most and low cards wrote my
name is recover but any phenomenal
dimensions
refraction or see what are you in or my
Luna monologue I didn't say my turn
acting phenom acaba relative again I'm
looking for instead of fractional in the
vertical dynamite Randall or grandmother
okay - those are associated with it
reflect refraction of late first one the
mullah reflection negative RNA incident
the red normally refer to play personnel
on the one legally imported lower body
ended in simply refracted ray and normal
to the interface of to transmit media at
the point of incidence or lie in the
same plane no instant ray refracted ray
and the normal to the interface of to
transfer and media at the point of
incidence or lie in same plane el lado
de Leon and Dawa okay I'm gonna second
de la vaca second law never imagined
reflection of a more angular of
incidence is equal to angle of
reflection another part another length
even and angle equal Allah other eternal
metric functioned a similar relation you
can and I get to grow antenna car in
down at the center body came in denial
over the well I and I a topic similar
similar story buddy Canada so I'm gonna
turn over in from sunshine what's I need
a I'm gonna sign you like are assigned a
bracket into brilliance Emma I could
have my angle of incidence or occurred
even by sign it
other Polly broccoli I was refreshed
nobody never they show no sign of a dig
a local degree and our Torah angle and
our thank you know another sine of an
angle divided by sine of another angle
on would at a for Matilda sign in a
bracket in rule over to another angle
now he recorded I know you thought like
well you like to sign of 1901 none other
world sine 45 designs exchange the sine
30 in there good about a different
channel on the myosin be the cyanide to
me mum lu- one on a Mac so marijuana
none upon the net sine of the angle of
incidence you are by sine of angle off
with fresh snow cones chin down on the
guitar in the corner catalonia numerous
safety first and second medium but LOL
first to middle second minute you see
right now i would have our gang of
instance the angle of friction oh no no
way the other I insisted you should tell
us where la now in divided Langille
Illuminism where other
the angle of the fraction one but say
what is our yoga son-in-law he might
ultimately tomorrow or tomorrow about
you are gonna automatic I dunno sinai by
sign are a poet constant that Delta now
the next sound what a mere exam Ron will
you kill him sign a divider time now
sign and ready to go good letter
maximally want no little minus one no I
didn't evaluate other but your ex
Aminata Mariana suppose Sinai divided
$10 - I dunno value to one of the caves
really neeyala I need somebody to sign
in divided to Indian key and
automatically I tomorrow sign or ma who
saw that that ratio are constantly are
the same ID be to econ standard America
never under the frack to index is it a
definition Allah
what do you mean Mary Fred next make you
more angle of the sine of the angle of
incidence by sine of angle of refraction
it is a Friday next nature market may be
the part of the in surah
what do you mean by refract next one on
next to open and discuss am on today so
we'll see lower the refractive index
nobody to refraction late late or it
nobody me there's no matter we really
probably to import and I'm gonna meet a
global Odom actually they travel giambo
all in the past the deviate to change
they love another but if I did I'm
cornered transparent electrons loosened
object my general but it's shown to
occur than opaque in America right now
chill alone are the new law related
traveling with you but to learn a people
our textbook you mention yonder than the
theorem refractive index will abide
round Frederickson day a concept about
negative sign a my side also the
definitional equation operator no order
parted
up on a board around the track next
ridiculous relate to you the flag to
index home button an absolute refractive
index animal relate your friend economic
appear in animals zero and the record it
in relation an automatic sidebar another
absolute reference name was symbolically
frightened national agenda so I'm aware
their fret next no para angle out animal
actually mention here the absolute
refractive index near relate to the
frantic some specific I to bother you
the friend X of this medium with respect
to the Atronach apart I'm gonna come
burial at the party calendar you'll mark
are thoroughly and what Sarah yourself
is you can a family so first job be the
refractive index you have already
stirred you that array of radiates
travels obliquely from one transparent
medium into another will change
direction in that second middle
near to al-saleem oh no we do not
instantly next fill it with foam under
the path changing or the bv3 animal
control the extent of the change in
direction that take place in take place
in a given pair of media is expressed in
terms of the fret next at rotolo it been
donnelly deviate a little bit adding
that will threaten sensory sadhana or
another okay
the constant appearing on the right hand
side of equation ten point four the ten
point four I can say the night we
constantly Ocwen Ameri with fragment
Excel
additionally at Ohlone deviation token L
upon a DVD the middle layer on moving
middle
yes they left is a wiki about extra
taller deviations are any given another
the concept when the banana refractive
index alert so given the word run now
the thread index can be linked to an
important physical quantity the relate
to speed of propagation of light in
different medium it turns out that late
propagates the difference will in
different media Lee it travels the
fastest in Viacom with the highest speed
of 3 into 10 raise to 8 meter per second
Neriah Naga England leg well Fred to
index an enemy to important that for a
physical conduct you mighty when the
Fatima tumor lady and item Ariana
quantity relate to speed a little speed
of my to the mocha panda but even our I
predict a medium refractive index net
what are you coming to now I related to
Moodle one of the every other summer
time a learn a little bit code Renault
massage that everywhere go donate total
spirit l wanna spoon a Ganesha already
equal or not back code to identify a
wanna do you need usually a Thomas
a lot of echo would immediately
I'm gonna wake up totally Devon a speed
and report to level 3 into 10 raised to
a 2 meter per second mingle of the net a
pseudo so according one Salam 3 lakh
kilo meter per second at an angle of
watch it a second Suzy on the nope can't
I wanted
late moon election 3 lakh club it
probably the nominee gonna reach over
speed in air the speed of it is only
marginally less compared to a coconut
angel movie accomplice will anybody to
come into a road coming to it reduces
considerably in glass or whatever share
glass 11 luckily only in my tutorials
friend immediately or SP
let the coroner said he glass water
along with my transparent meeting Allah
Allah Karim Allah change in them the
values reflect necks of a given pair of
media depend upon speed of light in the
to media as given below
but I'm not the Thunder and everybody
either medium one area medium 2 + / you
will die hey Dale is number little
fragments are gonna move on I get tired
I got under the MOOC before xml g glass
in the medium to india grandmother a
medium to window frame X number need
electricity Sava a little frightening
sana phenomena Google glass in the
refracted next time ing dare you
ok class in there in fact indexed and
there's another end the low voltage even
I am getting in any Martin earning in NW
thread of ID she whatever got no I wanna
reflect in Excel de relate to you
refractory index are what it shown it
came about and the medial cat eye level
to speed in the company similar for
example what are the agent open
n21 but they any why candelario
refractive index off total are like went
to LA but if readiness of second the
medium we trust 4 to 1 parents no no
random at immediately never flitting
service but any glass into the friend
sana kazi with respect to one on the
medium area like a era
other wanna end one to refrigerator so
first to medium with respect to second
oh mama time it is not a little rednecks
are if it's no como class in which no
penny question darling II question it
but the no self did you wanna know what
I'm really afraid to one my ladies
anyone and a mother you do this I done
down there a new over Atlanta and a
bunch of water into one idea one not
matter n1 - they get to one man in there
in the way I wanted to work my ideal the
speed of light in medium 1 upon England
now Rex samurai n 3 4 9 I didn't gel
happening on many other than the speed
of light in medium 4 divided by speed of
lady medium 3 odd case in X everybody an
angle to one I go to my other one no
deaths we're either tada - no let me
littlest Buda Buda you can simply be 1
by B - now geometric clear out of this
any and you know poster than N 1 2 and
even the reciprocal at the end
join uni namuci and the car you would
have a meeting one day around I don't
have to the friend sorry monkey question
okay commit and then a pattern that I
love idea number could it proved a
around a little oh what a kawarau is a
glass so I like it Diane went down next
to ironing a medium so we personally
burned
suppose you medium Errol and Gil so big
yeah I'm gonna come bear in a delay
would be maybe a bug la cinta refract
index but ironing lien to one in to what
they do about what about glass into the
fitness anaconda be thrust 50m and I on
the rope and Anya upper here my two
lately the tentative right except our
another minute Uncle Albert animal
agreement ginger yeah relate you've read
x-men la absolute refractive index would
have been a general at the example oh no
no no Posada ideally air in the speed /
air thank you mean it to the spill it in
the marina we literally lateness food
and Vanya other than will recap cell you
- threatening illegal is simply
refractive index an avocado okay I'm
careless food aggregation we're a couple
dozen or do not back until eight you
wanna split nobody know Tia see you know
it's it on a see in the value 3 into 10
raise to 8 meter per second okay over on
oka would happening like any American
car every table mattyc123 to become very
soon Allah upon Yanni your refractive
some glass knowledge another guild or
man and there's under the value CT of
Lading a Karen Daria this is equation
for 10 euro another
refract index of second a medium with
respect to what any with respect to one
than I ever lay a position each
absolutely friend miss in equation
pollen another turning a little Frank
absolutely refracting external a today
this city Kayla lady when a person goes
up iike a iabourer a mingle you know par
I am absolutely para a icon on the
bottom early any confusion mark on the
air or wacky tea whenever are turning
for today to year for even a man a local
spirit of lading medium one on our enemy
they want a la as an illiberal is the
speed of light in air I speed operator
medium Emilio a man a lot of
okay man and there's a model speed of
light in air onion recognition there's a
seal Elda
tarus period of etching medium put the
glass sonic speed of etching class i
Langley Mart running speed of raging
water about the animal is killed under
there from the equation that is C
divided by we united Tomas what about
this frightened Dixon with a man I
need to browse an effect on Man O'War
another one point two three three plus
into the 1.25 to come our facade are
materially glass in an aquatic or
delivery no other a particular signature
written in Corning refracted kaga 1.33
underwater Nell if I can close to 1.3 mm
1.5 million time brother lay the glass
in there no a little glass in it if they
really come if they don't know what okay
what island American apparently I don't
know given our mighty even you little
egg are under each question of a man is
figured out at our a Sweden apart in a
you never can set up a number on you
can't stand down a you with your own
moon ill developments NACA
okay you need the fragments in Islam
than a diamond Tucker optically by
Ingrid and Sarang you need acutally our
miracle arena para optically denser
medium may not possess greater mass
density for example kerosene a high elf
redness is optically denser than water
although its mass density is less than
water
what is the kind of animal food theater
quantity of our enough density Rho
density low optical density
eat then optical density on a circular
flight into a single mention of the name
tended me idiot occur or at this redneck
saku-dono
metalcore or until the little animal
oblique in a piranha
denser medium still a middleman
slaughter each other a legitimately
material layer of the medium prior are a
then B and C are the single achieved
erotic Anoka what okay okay you were a
very elevated porn I got a glass you can
upon PI a shaky gel Petrovic you a rarer
me didn't answer me did you go there
median glass been seven Arella class-
really so rarer medium is denser medium
what is our diamond city and learn about
the optical density and Ferelden at the
maturity refractive index N is a bandana
who does affect missin against the
frankness a comparatively koroneihana
you can under medium Anakin Barry and
then of the parameter a porta potti
should be joachim only way of lately
aired on the glass slick you gonna kill
other DVD enroll a eternal torment ie
deviation nor when the artistic turn on
or when the will talk why don't you
throw aluminum current normal daddy
thicken it down acidity porn department
I don't know normal target picture a bit
led is sitting not do it okay a data for
example if I walk turn arequipa warning
you were really doing that for one does
it but sure you're a capo easier to camp
in whatever we want to know or wonder if
you can already know a little bit about
it I think any money level what is then
selectively to pass symbol they bend it
towards the no I think Nina got emerald
or take care of it close the banister
with left no yeah then sir minimal Aisha
Tyler
I agree imaginary massive power lon
Rambabu Claro I see no William binocular
other ballot near the classroom will
conduct in which the condom other they
are immediate but I am a little a
particular Nicole Melissa
yet I could come at him then it's Air
America came back to a Paul Allen they
are in a normal that it will be similar
to they are Amelia nagito abrogation
loca then certain or did she not go
until they're not rapidly camera here
upon a normal night unanimity we cannot
get a bit rarer made it denser made it
to give only hill towards the normal
deflection Dawa deviation dhaba other
polite then survey did not make you a
delegate obey from the north nandanam
clear another about in the you topical
numbers job Ian Moir to no longer
excellence
I mean what's ago still someone for a
change and organ and Telemundo work in
already written up in the Polo minimal
could you fight questions early meaning
a man trip are you look important and so
say it said after and any other could
excuse o-negative to talk you know more
camera yeah
the Malaga until your stances on the
loop liberal stream but she's the
cardinal sin Cyrano see the guy in
yellow
I am sorry Luka mingler English Italy
and daily mistake another and oil in the
cockpit okay so question suppose to chin
area flake crowding air and this
obliquely into our top Selena angle
water equator and then that's the late
wave bend towards an oval or away from
normal white animal part of me pop our
little so you can have done it weighed
another and they have another water lake
and they do towards and away from the
wrong man opening Lee Hayden bender
garden and so it will become a delicious
to Gurudwara Midler Lincoln some sorry
candidate optical densities okay when a
ray of light enters from a optically
rarer medium to optically denser medium
the Ray bended towards the normal here
what reason of what reason optically
denser medium meant compared to here
therefore the ray of light will bend
towards the normal is Arnhem the idea
wanna mingle dancer okay the unalaq's
are attending later that's okay second
question
late tenders from air to glass having
the fraction x 1.5 so what is the speed
of light in the glass the speed of light
in vacuum is 3 into 10 raise to 8 meter
per second now Korea what a ton of the
glass in the redneck son about ng
thunder thunder ng is equal to C by V
normal equation okay LM Kenji Dalton
this seemed on Adam Lokhande I wanna VM
a single-phase you the can't defeated
and survey data find out from Table ten
point three the medium having highest
optical density also find the media with
the lowest optical density a forward a
no cabinet to bullet in CGI record of me
it on the delay now I'm underground 2.4
to eat tuna okay
another way I could avoid cranium the
one and a terrific next day naseeb I see
no one now gotta but whatever
the mayor no need to call it to cool the
diamond I never go anywhere textbook or
discussing under optical density cordon
of ammonia mass density vector quantity
Allah Allah Allah meaning in Cairo's
indicates led kerosene optically denser
on water my coordinates Arana pasha
namacarya Saad are many still intensity
of bar Tirana
given a column cordially cut-offs Nicole
called 11,900 England 9 click partition
relate to determine plate 2050 play
teleport tsunamis Eric you know about
our dynamic are about London City but
I'm gonna add and if you tell lemon to
the ever Oh tickle been city on and if I
don't know connect era of chicken
density curves in on water column
usually so tickle and sees you
Norman level a number of our nets are
now may change a pen city we are to the
end and subhana other hand premix a yes
then you are given Carol's in Tarpon in
and water in which of these decimal 8
travel faster use the information given
in table 10.3 was known on the top end
in another water movement under
Carol Sunita pending into today
other what about you know motor choices
really easy to travel yeah phenomenon
that I we question it ended immediately
to be frank missile and then speed of a
tournament in there I'm knockin at the
speed of latent median kana kana the
Mukhabarat to this but I'm glad the net
is Starla Luka they lead in another
corner moon never going to moon speed of
light in air by any material and Lincoln
speed of 80 million Rita a Pitino meters
the total coroner through totem our food
speed off late in the middle please say
Dylan Dawa one silhouettes organic
questa nm is equal to C by V Nellie we
got one day left and sneaky come on
cutter ve is equal to C by Yen Yen
Dimetrodon o coroner Tortola cool we
cool ependymal in AmeriCorps with a
military car and Amana the Frank index
of media buddy tomorrow eternally water
learn it to move smoothly they just
probably another 20 silica goes to mocha
refried uniform diameter is 2 point 4 2
what is the meaning of this statement in
the mocha I am that I am in refraction
execute a laverna each question can no
quranic ng illegal break glass indian
phenomenon i would lend a Linda but I am
going to
say to cool down think about
snow-clearing 2.42 something in there a
pollen the Fred mr. Underhill
Ethan Dino marbling yeah see corns -
Donna Evie come on yaar a ladies have
enough food to friend Roberto but I am
gonna leave right things wondering I
have them diamond doodle doodle a tip
honest will everyone already Korowai
answer them
we know that diamond is the hardest
material in yeah it will not help them
now from the fragrance of diamond one
thing is sure that then velocity or
speed by which light travels inside the
diameter is very really very low and
compared it to that of the velocity of
light in vacuum or am okay throw look at
it mainly only to travel a and Lana is
already an extra car not optical
refraction why spherical lenses on other
mechanics class at econo I've been there
to borrow some okra palapas children a
lock on the wall - you know the Nance
right ok we'll see you next video thank
you
[Music]